utsource.net 2009-06-29

# Privacy Statement

**UTSOURCE** protect our visitors' and customers' information, and do not disclose it to third parties.   
  
---  
**Information Gathering**  
Our site uses forms for visitors to request information, products, and services. We collect visitors' contact information, like their email address, in order to respond to their inquiries. We collect financial information, like their credit card numbers, as necessary to process orders. The only information our site collects is that which is supplied voluntarily by the visitor.   
**Web Site Visits**  
  
Welcome to utsource web site. At utsource, your privacy and the protection of your personal information is handled with great regard. The following text will inform you on how we use and manage the information collected at our site. 

Each time you visit utsource web site, our server automatically recognizes and logs your IP address. An IP address is basically the address of the computer making a request to our web server. No personal information or detail is obtained in this data interchange—a visitor's browser is not designed to provide this information. 

At utsource, logged IP addresses are periodically reviewed and analyzed in an effort to monitor, maintain, and effectively improve our Web site. This information is retained for no other purpose and is not shared outside of utsource. 

During a web site visit, we may ask a customer for contact information (email address, telephone number, fax number and addresses for shipping/billing). This information is collected on a voluntary basis—and only with customer approval. 

**Web Site Security**  
  
The utsource web site contains links to other web sites. utsource does not control or take responsibility for personal information collected on these sites nor is utsource responsible for the accuracy or the content of these sites.

This Site contains content, services, advertising and other materials that link to Web sites operated by third parties. We have no control over those other sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. We encourage you to refer to the privacy policies, if any, of those sites. 

When accessing our online order entry system using a secure browser, one can feel secure transmitting credit card or other confidential information sent over the Internet.

**Cookies**  
  
Cookies are simple text files stored on a visitor's computer. Cookies are just as safe as any other data stored on a computer. Cookies are created by web sites and used to store data for the convenience of the visitor. A cookie cannot be used by a web site other than the one that created it. A cookie cannot be used to read data from your computer other than the data stored in the cookie. The only data stored in our cookies is data we selectively choose to store in cookies from among the data you enter on our web site. Our site does not use cookies to store financial information, contact information, or other personal or sensitive data. Our site uses cookies only to remember our visitors' and their preferences and to deliver content specific to their needs.

**Note:** We reserve the right to make changes to our privacy policy at any time without prior notification.
